You
let's see here assemble in front of the clubhouse at 6 p.m. sharp looks like I've got some time to
kill the tryouts were tough I wonder if any of the other guys got accepted too
Tachibana Otomo I'd better see you here the first team is using the main field right now is that what
they were talking about oh that guy plays for Japan's national team a bunch of them are players
I've only ever seen on TV and now I get to watch them practice right in front of me
hey aren't you that loud guy who was at the youth club trail those bags are you moving into the
dorms you got accepted am I right oh uh yeah yay congratulations I knew you'd be able to make
the cut I thought you played most impressively I hope you move up to the first team one day
huh oh this is probably your first time seeing them practice right uh yeah we don't have this
stuff in ehime ah is that so well I'm sure you'll get used to it in no time and because the fields
are right next to each other the members of the youth team get to see firsthand how the j-league
regulars and other top-ranked athletes train if you're super lucky they'll even give you pointers
at times just another perk to feed on the youth team awesome so cool I'm so freaking lucky I can't
believe I'm going to be playing soccer in this kind of environment huh oh yeah that's right you
didn't know Otomo and I checked and it turns out we were the only ones to get signed on from our group
that's what you get for not exchanging numbers with everyone
doesn't feel good being left out does it wait so does that mean you guys are going to be living in
the dorms too yeah even though Asakusa isn't too far away I figured if I lived here I could motivate
myself to work even harder me too instead of spending time just commuting I can utilize it
to train more also staying home would have made me soft still that's nothing compared to you coming
all the way from ehime I'm so happy that you guys are here seriously hey if you don't mind could I
please have your autographs I want to get the very first autographs from Asperion's next generation of
star players sure don't see why not and this will be a good way to commemorate the moment reuniting with
my brothers in arms my dude how can you say that with a straight face huh what did I say something
wrong just now so do I just write my name here yeah it'd be great if I could get all of your
autographs on the same page oh that's just some tracing paper please leave it where it is
that autograph is special it's gonna be valuable in the future for sure could it by Ashi seriously
dude are you messing with me do any research into the team you're joining look he's over there
they even wrote a full-page thread about him he's incredible he's a first-year but he gets to
practice with the first team this guy's only a year older than me and it looks like there's a direct
path from J youth to going pro if you play well it doesn't matter how old you are they'll even let
a high schooler play in the J League but yeah she's already got a bunch of diehard fans you support him
from that alone you can tell he's an exceptional player there are people who say that he's the
future star of not only Esperion but Japan's national team Haruhisa Kurebayashi
wait a sec I know you you're the guys who made it through the tryouts whoa and you were on the team we
played against yo Asuri looks like they're moving into the dorms too why don't you say hello you're too
loud he's a grumpy Gus I play defense during tryouts but I'm really a forward the name's Yuma how you
doing a forward huh sorry to say this but I'll be replacing you soon I'm Ashito Ali if you haven't
heard of me I'm a once-in-a-millennium genius Ford these guys outrank us you idiot you can't say
those things to them you're misunderstanding something here we're from the junior youth team
Asuri and I are in the same grade as you the youth team was short a couple of players so they had us
sub in during the tryouts right oh this one's Asuri his dad's actually in English Yuma I don't need
you to introduce me I'm June marks Asuri I played forward against you during tryouts but I'm usually
a defender hello hello nice to meet ya handsome and good at soccer there's no way he's a decent person
he's definitely an enemy amazing if you two are already training with the Asperion youth team they
must be expecting a whole lot from you guys much respect I played with the Yokoyama Musashino team
I'm Soichiro Tachibana from now on we're comrades playing on the same team and I hope I can learn a
lot from you guys nice to meet you geez it's already past six o'clock but we're still missing one person
wait how many players are living in the dorms there are ten the entire junior youth team except Asuri and Yuma
have already gotten their kits and have just moved into their rooms the last player we signed is someone
we scouted but I can't reach him right now already a headache oh well I'll get you guys your kits and
training gear then you can get settled in wait we get gear you mean jerseys and stuff huh
um you see I thought that I needed to earn my jersey by becoming a starter in that case I'm gonna
need a little time to pick up some money you all receive kits and training gear it's part of the
program if you leave them outside of your room in the morning the dorm staff will wash them for you
if they rip or you grow out of them let us know when we'll give you new ones
oh wait the guy who isn't here yet is actually supposed to be your roommate think you could
possibly bring his to the room with you oh also
your dorm was originally built with the J League players in mind and fun fact it used to house the
first team it's got a ton of amenities from a cafeteria to meeting rooms as well as a full-scale
training room all that for just 5,000 yen a month I honestly wish I could live here
this place is incredible they've made it so that I don't have to worry about anything
all right you ready give us your name and number nice and loud Ashito Aoi with Tokyo's
Asperion Youth Soccer I'll be number 33 they didn't tell us we'd be doing a photo shoot it's
nerve-racking I mean it is on the schedule dude it's for the official player directory I've been
awake since 6 this morning trying to get my hair to stand up just right here this is from last year
check it out J League clubs publish these player directories for the fans they love this stuff there's
a section for youth players so the next one is deaf gonna have her pictures in it I've got to send
one to my mom by the way I've been meaning to ask you what's your roommate like he was the only player
to get scouted well he never actually showed up really I can't believe someone would be this late
apparently his name's Togashi I'm kind of worried you think he's all right Aoi Otomo good morning I want to
introduce you to my roommate oh hi there my name's Kanpei Kuroda from the junior youth team Tachibana
told me you three made it through the tryouts that's more than usual which is actually kind of
funny only nine from the junior team moved up right Ashito Aoi I'm from Ehime Ehime you know Kuroda I just
gotta say something the way you junior youth guys only stick together isn't very cool come on I know
you have all been playing together for a long time or whatever you guys don't need to treat us like
we're total strangers know what I mean right but most of us aren't great at that kind of stuff Yuma's
pretty comfortable around people as much as he likes to joke around he's a real solid player Takashima is
Yuma's best friend I guess he can be pretty social too Asari would be the last person I think of though
just look at that perfect little face of his so what you're saying is you all keep to yourselves
it doesn't help that everyone's feeling a little nervous right now nervous can't blame us one of
our dreams comes true today you know their dream
this year we're pleased to welcome 13 new players to the Spirion youth team we'd like to recognize all
their hard work and give congratulations my name's Aki Tsukashima nice to meet you I'm a youth team
alumnus and one of the coaches if you have any questions at all don't hesitate to ask the dream
Kuroda mentioned it was to join the Spirion youth team right the junior youth players must have gone
through a test to get promoted too and from what that old geezer said half of them didn't make the cut
I'm sure the selection process to get here was really tough but isn't the point of this to go
pro I'm not even close to achieving my dream how can these guys say they've reached their goal how
complacent can you get my name's Diego Benson I'm the goalkeeper coach but I'm more than happy to help
out all our players as long as once you go I saw them at tryouts too they really are nice people
hello everyone I'm head coach Nozomi Dante you'll be seeing more of me than any of the other Spirion
coaches you know why that's because I'll be in charge of the V team for our youth soccer club just like in
the pro leagues I knew it youth teams are different from normal high school sports clubs they have
fewer members but every one of them is highly skilled and even though there are 40 players on the team
only some of them get to play in official matches of course those who perform well on the B team
sorry I'm late that's my bad we'll be promoted to the A team where they'll have a chance to work
with him I'm the youth team manager Tatsuya Fukuda it's nice to meet you I'll take you to the world stage
oh my what's that racket
thanks for one hell of a send-off
I'll never forget you right on lads
Kiji Togashi I'm a center back for the youth team
and now that I'm here I'm gonna lead the team all the way to the top that's my promise to you
hold on is that young man really on the youth team
I heard that they scouted
what the heck were they thinking
Togashi I thought I made myself very clear
if you want to play soccer you have to quit the biker gang
they just came to see me off
it's like they pulled this guy straight out of a cartoon
is this some kind of joke he's the only player they scouted this year
here I'm your roommate Ashito Aoi it's nice to meet you
I've been waiting to give this to you
also the old man was just about to say something when you interrupted him
I really wanted to hear it so get changed and sit down so we can continue okay
I'm curious you promoted from the junior youth team
uh no I got accepted after going through the tryouts
right on good to hear
thanks for holding on to this for me
I'm Kiji Togashi glad to be roomies with you Aoi
same call me Ashito
that's weird he looks like a punk but he's super nice
good to hear
does that mean he's got some kind of beef with the players from the junior youth team
what's going on
hey Aoi
I'd be careful around him
huh
that guy
isn't someone you should put your trust in
our manager Fukuda is one of the best coaches in the nation
and specializes in developing young talent
Nazemi
because of his reputation
Esperion gets hundreds of applications each year
from young players who specifically want to learn from him
and as manager Fukuda always says
we shouldn't bother with players we can control
to compete on the world stage we need players who can surpass our expectations and surprise us
it's because of this philosophy
that manager Fukuda is able to discover so many talented and unconventional players
whom other teams have overlooked
and yet more often than not
it is precisely those players that grow into leaders for Esperion's youth and first teams
for years now I've seen what he can do firsthand
and I know this for a fact
the best way to develop the talents of all our players
is to have an open mind and always examine the bigger picture
okay you can handle it from here can't you
yeah
uh
all right
how about a quick match
but with just the new players
hey where are you going
what's with you man
I thought you'd be the most pumped up for this
I'm good
I just wanted to focus
so I thought I'd be alone for a bit
don't forget what the manager Fukuda said
if we play well
we'll get promoted directly to the A-team
make sure you get warmed up all right
with that promotion on the line
people are already tense
you can tell just how much everyone wants it
though for some players resting until the game starts works best
anyway I'll leave and let you focus
hey bro
who called out for a delivery
you've got what now
are you kidding me
bro
you're the one who asked me to make a lunch for you
I don't think so
I had an extra class this morning you jerk
you have any idea how early I had to wake up to make this
I'm sorry Hana
I already ate with the new players in the cafeteria
why am I surprised
this is exactly why you can't find anyone to settle down with you big dummy
sorry it's my fault
I was the one who asked Fukuda to get you to come over here today
huh
the daughter of the president of Kaido Electric is coming to visit us
so I was hoping that you could keep her company
do I have to
we don't get along
come on please
you're around the same age
also Kaido's our sponsor
forget about that boring stuff Hana
can you believe it
Nozomi said something nice about me at the meeting
I had to pinch myself
I thought I was dreaming
I only said that
because the parents were losing faith in us
ugh stop being so handsy
speaking of the meeting
your match announcement certainly came as a surprise
a surprise match?
oh that's right
I told them that if they played well
they'd be promoted to the A team tomorrow
which of course definitely got their attention
I want to make it clear
I'm against them playing a match so soon
they all still need time to adjust
but if we don't do this
it'll take forever for them to get used to each other
that's why we'll just make them play together
this is the best way to teach them
well I guess one game wouldn't hurt
and it seems there's some tension between the new players
well if you need anything else from me
I'll be eating alone
I finally get to see you again
but it's always soccer this and soccer that with you
hey bro
you should visit home every once in a while
I know it's kinda awkward for you
but too bad
cause mom misses you
by the way Fukuda
I've been meaning to ask you something for a while now
that boy you brought in here from Ehime
you know the really loud one
Ashito Aoi
do you intend on favoring him
or giving him special treatment?
me?
of course not
you know I'm not the kind of coach
that would do something like that
come on
in that case let me be frank
ever since the tryouts
I've been certain of one thing
unless he improves at a miraculous rate
there's no way he's going pro
even if he puts his all into training
in three years
he still won't be good enough to move up to the A-team
this Ashito Aoi might become your very first failure Fukuda
Boo!
I thought you left
I'm just surprised
and it seems kind of unfair
to say that about a player
who only joined the team today
wouldn't you say?
also
I am a fan of Ashito Aoi
probably his first in the world
wow
you
Next time on Ao Ashi, the first youth match.